<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Chaotic Focus - Cycling</title><link href="http://www.chaoticfocus.net/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://www.chaoticfocus.net/feeds/cycling.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://www.chaoticfocus.net/</id><updated>2017-10-06T10:00:00-04:00</updated><entry><title>Relighting the Fire</title><link href="http://www.chaoticfocus.net/posts/2017/10/relighting-the-fire/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-10-06T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-10-06T10:00:00-04:00</updated><author><name>Noel</name></author><id>tag:www.chaoticfocus.net,2017-10-06:/posts/2017/10/relighting-the-fire/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;My offseason came pretty suddenly for me this year.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My offseason came pretty suddenly for me this year. I started off the early Cyclocross season
motivated and then... nothing. I finished my first two races, no real problems even though I was
finishing much farther back than I expected. That said, I'm not sure &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; I thought I'd finish
farther up the field since my weight has been creeping upwards for months and I know I race much
better 20 lbs lighter than I am right now. I know: shocking, right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, my first two races were nothing to write home about but no real issues. Saturday's race on
the second race weekend frankly sucked. Half the course was composed of rooty singletrack that was
no fun to ride on a CX bike and I just wasn't having fun. I finished on the lead lap, unlike a
number of folks, but other than that there was nothing good to say about the race. Sunday's race was
at the same venue and I honestly just had no interest in getting up and going. That quickly morphed
into having no real interest in the bike at all for about the next week. I'd look at it and think "I
really need to ride" followed immediately by "Meh." and then I'd go do something else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After several days of that I got in touch with my coach and told him I hid end-of-season burnout and
just couldn't find any interest in riding. He was a little surprised but I only started working with
him back in May and I guess he hadn't realized I've been training since last November and racing
since the end of March. To him, we'd only been working for three or four months, to me I'd been
working for going on 10. The good news is that after basically a week off the bike I started really
wanting to ride again, and especially feeling the urge to ride my mountain bike for the first time
since April. The bad news is that the timing was kinda bad since I had to go to Chicago for &lt;a href="http://www.weftec.org"&gt;WEFTEC
2017&lt;/a&gt; about two weeks after that third race. That meant I didn't really ride
for a week, got a few days on the bike, then I was off the bike for another week while I was in
Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So here I am, freshly returned from Chicago, and I'm excited to ride but (even more) overweight and
probably missing a ton of hard-earned fitness. Oh well, it is what it is, I suppose. I am motivated
and ready to ride again, and I'm ready to get back into the gym for the offseason weight training so
I guess that's all good news too. I kinda feel like the 2018 season starts next week.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="cycling"></category><category term="offseason"></category></entry></feed>